[bright music]
Hi, how can I help you?
Marlboros.
Come again?
Can I get some Marlboros? Are you deaf?
Uh…
One pack?
No, just a loosie.
Are you fucking kidding me, right now?
You’re really just gonna give me a loosie?
Sorry, I thought ‘loosie’ meant stick.
In the Philippines, we actually
sell cigarettes by the stick.
I don't care wherever the hell you're from.
If you don’t know anything about
this country, why even come here?
[suspenseful music]
I don't like that. It's opened.
Give me a new one.
Will that be cash or card?
Cash!
Idiot.
You can remove it.
Fucking Asian.
Excuse me, what did you just call me?
I said fucking Asian.
Do you have a problem with that?
Yeah.
Maybe I do!
Then why don't you go back to China?
You don't belong here!
Maybe 'cause I'm not from China.
I'm from the Philippines.
What did you say?
I said I'm not from China.
I'm from the Philippines!
It's the same fucking
difference, you idiot!
[suspenseful music]
I'm back.
Andre?
Hello?
Where are you?
What happened to your face?
Nothing.
Turn around.
I'm busy.
Look at me.
I said I'm busy.
What happened to you?
You can’t fight with robbers here, okay?
They carry guns. You could’ve gotten shot.
It wasn’t a robber.
Who did this to you?
Did...
Did you get into a fight with a customer?
I knew it.
I knew I couldn’t trust you with the store!
You... you're arrogant and
impulsive and irresponsible!
What did you do to the customer?
I told him he should know the difference
between the Philippines and China.
What?
[piano music]
[applause]
Oh, wow!
Uh, thank you.
Thank you to the Hollywood Prestige
International Short Film Festival.
Um, shoutout to everyone – staff
and organizers who put this together.
And, of course, this one goes out to
all the aspiring filmmakers and artists.
Anyone whose voice has never been heard,
anyone who feels unrecognized out there,
this one’s for you. And...
Oh my God!
Just thank you to Hollywood for
opening doors for more people like us.
Thank you, thank you.
More love. Woah!
[applause]
Hey,
you're the filmmaker
from the Philippines, right?
Oh, uh...
I'm Ethan Bloom, with Hollywood Prestige.
I’m so sorry. I didn’t…
No worries. I just wanna
come over and congratulate you.
I saw your short.
I was really blown away.
That was great work.
Oh, wow. Uh...
Thank you. Coming from a Hollywood
Producer like yourself, that means a lot.
Don't mention it.
So who are you here with?
Just by myself.
Hm… And how long are you
planning to stay here in LA?
Just a couple of days.
That’s too bad.
Why?
Well, I’m working on a special project and…
I’d like you to be a part of it.
Oh.
But listen, I got to get going.
I got a meeting with Tarantino.
And yeah, I’m gonna be late.
Can we meet tomorrow,
talk about this a little more?
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
Great! How’s 3pm at
the Ponti’s? You know it?
Yeah, yeah.
In the meantime, check out
my website. It’s on the card there.
Okay, yeah. I will do. Thank you so much.
Alright. See you tomorrow.
[indistinct chatter]
He said my directing style...
was masterful!
Masterful?
And he wants me to be a
part of his upcoming project!
OMG bestfriend!
“Pia Wurtzbach” is in tears.
As in!
The Miss Universe of your life is sobbing!
I told you bestfriend,
if something’s meant for you,
destiny will find a way to make it happen.
And besides, you really
belong there in America.
Even if your Caucasian father
doesn’t want to recognize you,
no one can deny that you’re
a true-blooded American!
Can we please not talk
about unnecessary people?
You’re ruining the moment.
Sorry, bestfriend.
My apologies.
[playful music]
If I were you, I won’t
let that opportunity pass.
Give it your best shot!
I’m not sure bestfriend.
What? Why hesitate?
People in Hollywood are chasing after you!
Not everyone gets an offer from Hollywood!
I know. But everything’s expensive here.
The motel where I’m staying at, it's...
150 dollars a night.
That’s 7,500 pesos.
A night!
I can’t afford to stay
here that much longer.
I’ll run out of money.
Why ask for an advance payment
from that Hollywood Executive?
Ask for his help.
I’m not sure.
I don’t think so.
It’s embarrassing.
But you should find a way, bestfriend.
You’re an award-winning
filmmaker for God’s sake!
If I were the one with the
Hollywood offer, I’d do anything,
even if that means borrowing
money from relatives!
[door opens]
[shower running]
[tiping]
Hello?
Hi. Uh, I saw your post online.
You’re looking for a roommate, right?
Yeah, um...
it’s 12 month minimum.
I only accept cash.
Oh, but I only need a place for two weeks.
I thought you said you saw the ad?
I did.
Okay, well, it says a 12 month minimum.
I get that but the thing is
I’m just staying here for a few days.
After that, I'm flying
back to the Philippines.
You’re from the Philippines?
Yeah.
Ah… We can do 750 for two weeks.
You’re kidding, right?
What the fuck?
I don’t have time for prank callers.
No, I’m not a prank caller.
Look, you advertised the
room for a thousand dollars.
So I thought, two weeks, that would be 500.
Makes sense, right?
I don’t have time for this.
It’s two in the morning.
I have to go to sleep.
Oh wait. No, no.
The thing is I only have 400 dollars.
Which means you can’t afford the room,
which means I can’t accommodate you.
Please.
I just need a temporary place to stay
while doing this project in Hollywood.
You’re doing a Hollywood project?
Yeah, that’s why I’m extending my stay.
Are they gonna pay you?
Yeah, but compensation
comes after the work is done.
Are you sure about that?
100 percent.
Okay, we can do 650 for the two weeks.
It’s final offer.
But I told you I only have 400...
Take it or leave it.
Okay. I’ll take it.
Okay.
We can meet at a coffee shop near my place.
You have to show me that you have the money
or I’m not letting you into my apartment.
Okay, uh...
what’s the location of the coffee shop?
I'll text you more info tomorrow.
Okay, but you are sure
you're gonna be there, right?
Because once I leave my motel,
I’m not gonna have anywhere else to go.
If you have the money,
you have nothing to worry about.
Okay, but what if I were to…
Hello?
Well, see you tomorrow.
[street noise]
Oh, shit.
Wait, hey!
Shit.
You look tired.
We should get some drinks.
Oh, uh...
I'm... I’m actually good.
How about something to eat?
I actually ate just before I got here.
Andre,
you’re gonna have to get
familiar with how we do things here.
This is Hollywood.
All of our meetings involve food and drink.
Well, in that case, um,
I’ll have what you’re having.
Good boy.
Waiter!
Hi. What can I get you today?
We’ll have whatever
the chef is recommending
and a bottle of the Claret please.
I’ll be right back for that.
Thank you.
So, here's the thing.
You know how exclusive Hollywood is, right?
And you know that not
everyone that wants to work here
gets the chance to really work here.
A beginner like you,
you need connections.
Powerful connections.
That's why I’m offering you this project.
I want you to be a part
of an exclusive group.
It's called the Hollywood Elite Club.
Now, I don't offer this to just anyone.
I only offer this to people
I really want to work with.
And after seeing your
short, I knew right away,
you're the guy I'm looking for.
And you're timing,
it’s just perfect.
Hollywood is all about
diversity these days.
We need more people of
color like you in the industry.
And coming straight from the Philippines,
I believe you can offer a
very unique artistic
and cultural perspective
that no one else could.
You will be in demand.
Those Hollywood Executives?
Yeah, they’ll be chasing you down,
begging you to work with them.
Within a month of joining
the Hollywood Elite Club,
you're gonna be rubbing elbows with
Ryan Reynolds, Ryan Gosling...
Ryan Seacrest?
Of course, Ryan Seacrest!
All the Ryans!
Alright, the biggest celebrities, producers,
directors, writers in the industry.
No, don’t do that.
Don’t cry.
I haven't even dropped the bomb yet.
After you join the Hollywood Elite Club,
you’re going to have the opportunity
to make the kind of money you
never dreamed you could make!
So how do I join this Hollywood Elite Club?
Good question.
Right now, because I
believe deeply in my heart
that you’re talented, you’re hardworking,
you've got what it takes,
you’re automatically a member of the club.
Wow, uh,
I don’t know what to say.
Hm… I bet you don’t.
But here… here's the catch, okay?
In order for you to do these projects with
talent, executives from the biggest film
and television companies here in Hollywood,
you need to upgrade the membership.
Okay, how do I do that?
The question my friend
is are you willing to do it?
Yeah, of course.
I’m willing to do anything.
Here’s your wine.
Thank you. You can just leave the bottle.
Alright, enjoy.
Thank you.
Andre,
I want you to trust me
when I tell you
this is, in fact,
the best decision you’ll ever make.
Cheers.
[bright music]
Hello, who's this?
Hey, are you still interested in the room?
Oh, yeah... Of course, I am!
Okay, cool, um...
meet me at The Barista in ten minutes.
Where's that?
Is this your first time using Google Maps?
Well, uh, no…
No.
The thing is I’m on my
way back to my motel.
Can we just meet in an hour instead?
Uh, I can't. I have work.
Uh, what about in thirty minutes?
Are you sure you can
be there in thirty minutes?
Yeah, yeah, I'm sure. I’ll be there.
Okay, um, I’ll see you there.
Okay, see you. Bye.
[bright music]
How are you?
Good, how about you?
I'm just getting started for the day.
I‘m coming from another gig.
Oh,
working hard, huh?
L.A life.
You get it.
Hmm…
Not really.
I'm not from here.
Really?
Yeah, I’m from the Philippines.
How long have you been in LA?
It's just my second day.
Well, welcome to Los Angeles.
How are you liking it so far?
I like it a lot!
Everyone here is so kind and helpful.
Well,
except for this
one guy I'm about to meet.
I saw his ad online,
advertising his place
as cheap and affordable
but it was $1000 a month
to share a one-bedroom.
And he wanted a 12-month
lease with one month
security deposit, one
month’s rent, and all that.
So since I only needed two
weeks, I asked if I could pay 500,
because half of a thousand’s 500.
You know how much he charged me instead?
650 dollars!
What a selfish, greedy bastard!
You know, I know you’re new here,
but I’d be very careful of
how I talk about other people,
even the greedy, selfish ones.
You never know whose help
you’re gonna end up needing.
I don’t think I’m ever gonna
need help from this guy.
He’s really just after my money.
650 for two weeks, that’s
less than 50 bucks a night.
That’s not bad, especially
considering the inconvenience
of letting someone stay with
you for a short amount of time.
Why are you getting so...
Because that greedy selfish
bastard you’re talking about...
it’s me.
I don't think we need to
meet at The Barista anymore.
But no, I don't have anywhere else to stay.
[bright music]
Look, I’m so sorry. I had no idea that...
This is just 300.
No, but I gave the rest of my
money to this Hollywood Executive.
Are you fucking with me?
No, I’m not lying.
Earlier today, I met him and I
had to give him all my money.
And why did you give him you’re money?
Because I wanna be part
of this Hollywood Elite Club.
What’s that?
It's this exclusive membership
that would allow me
to work with film and
production companies here in LA.
How much did you pay him?
3000 dollars.
But it’s worth it, right?
I really wanna give Hollywood a shot.
So you didn't have money to pay rent,
but you had 3000 dollars
for whatever that is?
It's my mom's.
She works in the Middle East and
she sends me her savings every month.
Whatever.
300… I guess that means
you can stay with me for one week.
But -
Half of 650 is 325.
I’m giving you a great deal here.
You get an air bed.
Um, I'll give you some
blankets and pillows.
Uh, you can use the fridge,
uh, any of the utensils in the kitchen.
Just wash them after
you’re done using them.
Laundry is downstairs.
And I will give you your own keys tomorrow.
Are you sure you still want me to stay?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure,
especially since I’m just after your money.
I’m sorry if I…
If I were you, I would just stop.
Oh, and another piece of friendly advice
from someone who's greedy and selfish,
be careful of hustlers, alright?
They’ll...
They’re all over the place in Hollywood.
What do you mean?
Uh, swindlers, fraudsters,
professional scammers.
They'll deceive you – make you think
they’ll help you achieve your
Hollywood dreams or whatever, but...
in reality, they're just after your money.
Hollywood scam
[tiping]
We’re unable to complete your call.
To speak to a customer
service representative...
That was my mom’s savings.
She worked hard for that for many years.
She’s planning to retire
from work after a few years
but now, I’ve lost all her money.
I’m so stupid.
I don’t know what to do.
I don't wanna go back to the
Philippines without my mom's money.
I need to find that swindler!
I'll never forgive myself if I
just lose my mom's savings.
Don’t you know how to pump?
Okay, let me do it.
Observe, so you’ll know
how to do it yourself.
This goes in here.
[machine running]
Something the matter?
Uh... No.
Then...
I’m just adjusting to the weather.
You know what, I can do it.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Thank you for your help. I appreciate it.
Go back to sleep. I’m good.
Okay, I can’t sleep while this is going.
Can you just…
[bright music]